太棒了
Great.
让我换一下底片  好
Great. Just give me a sec to change film. Okay.
我知道你不希望我知道
Okay. I know I'm not supposed to know,
但我知道了  我真为你感到高兴
but I do and I'm so excited for you.
什么回事
What's going on?
莫妮卡怀孕了
Monica's pregnant.
天啊  所以说你们两个是奉子成婚
Oh, my God. Is that why you guys had to get married?
我没有怀孕
Guys, I'm not pregnant.
精子游得太慢了
Oh, slow swimmers?
什么  你这是什么意思  你没有怀孕吗
What?! What do you mean? You're not pregnant?
你没跑去跟别人说我怀孕了吧
You didn't tell anybody I was, did you?
没有
No.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我们来拍张莫妮卡跟英勇士兵的合照
Why don't we get a shot of Monica and the bloody soldier.
说起这点  乔伊你得在婚宴开始前换套衣服
About that, Joey, you have to change before the party.
不行  我没带衣服来换
I can't. I don't have any other clothes here.
那就拜托去找套衣服
Find some, please.
别再穿着"我不幸战死于法国"的衣服了
Anything that doesn't say, "I died tragically in France."
我们让新人跟伴娘们合照一些照片吧
Why don't we see the bride and the groom, and the bridesmaids.
莫妮卡  你为什么告诉大家你没有怀孕
Hey, Mon, why'd you tell the guys that you weren't pregnant?
因为我本来就没怀
Because I'm not.
我们发现了你的验孕棒  如果你没有怀孕...
We found your tests. If you're not pregnant...
那是因为我怀孕了
...it's because I am.
你在胡说什么  菲比  你在胡说什么
What are you talking about? Phoebe, what are you talking about?
对  我怀了孩子
Yes, I am with child.
我不想说  因为今天是你们的大喜之日
I didn't want to say anything because it's your day.
我不想抢了你的风采
I didn't wanna steal your thunder.
于是你就告诉大家我怀孕了
So you told people I was pregnant?
你觉得这种对话  我会想要记录下来吗
Does this look like a conversation I want to remember?
孩子他爸是谁  对啊
Who's the father? Yeah.
我不能说
I can't say.
为什么   为什么不行
Why? Why not?
我不能说  因为他是名人
I can't say because he's famous.
天啊  是哪个名人
Oh, my God. Who is it?
菲比  你得告诉我们
Phoebe, come on, you have to tell us.
好吧  是詹姆斯.布洛林
Okay, okay, it's James Brolin.
詹姆斯.布洛林是孩子的爸爸
James Brolin is the father of my baby.
你指的是芭芭拉·史翠珊的老公詹姆斯·布洛林
As in Barbra Streisand's husband James Brolin?
什么
What?!
他从没跟我提过这事
Well, he never said that to me.
《老友记》  第八季  第1集  在说了"我愿意"之后
Friends S08E01 The One After I Do
莫妮卡  请你先到旁边
Monica, if you step away,
我们要拍钱德勒跟伴娘的合照  好
we'll get Chandler and the bridesmaids. Okay.
何不只拍伴娘的合照呢
How about just the bridesmaids?
我是新郎  听说这个角色很重要
You know, I am the groom. I was told it was a big deal.
没错  对
It is. Yeah.
天啊
Oh, my God.
谢谢你  我现在还没有办法处理这件事
Thank you for that. I just can't deal with this just quite yet.
于是你告诉我莫妮卡怀孕了
So instead you told me Monica was pregnant?
是你说她怀孕了  我只是没反驳你罢了
You said she was. I just didn't disagree with you.
真狡猾  是啊
Sneaky. Yeah.
笑一个  姑娘们
Smile, ladies!
詹姆斯.布洛林  亏你想得出  我知道
By the way, James Brolin? I know.
我脑海里只蹦出两个人名
I could only think of two names:
他跟小艾德·贝格利
Him and Ed Begley Jr. And then...
我记得他是男同志  所以...
I remembered he's gay, so...
小艾德·贝格利不是男同志
Ed Begley Jr. is not gay.
真的吗
Really?
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
先生们女士们  我非常荣幸地
Ladies and gentlemen, it gives me great pleasure to introduce to you
首次向大家介绍  钱德勒·宾夫妇
for the very first time: Mr. And Mrs. Chandler Bing.
到舞池前  我要送你一份礼物
Before we go out there, I got a present for you.
我才不要把手伸到你的口袋里
Honey, I'm not gonna put my hand in your pocket.
不是  我去上了舞蹈课  什么
No. I've been taking dancing lessons. What?
我上了六星期的舞蹈课
For the last six weeks.
我希望这一刻能让你永生难忘
I wanted this to be a moment you'd never forget.
真的是太体贴了
That is so sweet.
你愿不愿意以夫妻的身份跟我跳第一支舞
So would you care to join me in our first dance as husband and wife?
我愿意
Yes.
怎么了
What's the matter?
我的新鞋太滑了
It's these new shoes, they're all slippery.
你还能跳舞吗  不太行
Are you gonna be able to do this? Not well.
好消息是我觉得没人在看我们
Well, the good news is, I don't think anyone's looking at us.
你准备好要谈谈了吗
So are you ready to talk about it?
没有
No.
现在呢
Now?
我不要谈
No!
我们来谈别的事  谢谢
We'll talk about something else then. Thank you.
孩子他爸是谁
Who's the father?
亲爱的  我还没有告诉他
Honey, I haven't told him yet...
我打算先告诉他  再告诉其他人
...so, until I do, I don't think I should tell anybody else.
没关系  那很合理
Yeah. That's fine. That's fair.
是泰格吗  菲比
Is it Tag? Phoebe!
好吧  对不起  我不问了
Okay, I'm sorry. I'll stop.
是罗斯吗  是罗斯吧
Is it Ross? It's Ross, isn't it?
天啊  是乔伊  别说了  好吗
Oh, my God, it's Joey! Stop it. Okay?
在告诉他之前我不会告诉你的
I am not gonna tell you until I tell him.
至少我们知道他是个男的
At least we know it's a him.
天啊
Oh, sweet Lord.
对不起  好吗  我跑到礼品店
I'm sorry, okay? I went down to the gift shop.
那里只卖这个跟浴袍
It was either this or a bathrobe.
你更看重哪点呢  是我的穿着打扮
Look. What's more important: the way I'm dressed,
还是我能出席你的婚礼
or being with you on your special day?
我都懒得假装刚才在听你说话
Honey, I'm not gonna even pretend I was listening. Hey! Hey!
我是罗斯  我们应该没有见过
I'm Ross, I don't believe we met.
我是莫妮卡的哥哥
I'm Monica's older brother.
我是她在餐厅的同事蒙娜
Hi, I'm Mona from her restaurant.
你好  她在餐厅的同事蒙娜
Hello, Mona from her restaurant.
蒙娜  这个名字很美
Mona. What a beautiful name.
是吗  我一直都很讨厌这个名字
You think so? I always kind of hated it.
少来了  蒙娜丽莎
Come on! Mona Lisa.
蒙娜...
Mona...
利格拉齐
...Llegglachen.
她是着名的植物学家
The famous botanist.
不  她...她死了  但是
Oh, no, she's... Well, she's dead now, but...
她曾经是植物学界最性感的女人
Supposedly she was once quite the hottie of the plant world.
真的吗
Really?
我根本不认识她  琳达·利格拉齐
See, I never knew about her. Linda Llegglachen...
你在几号桌
So, what table are you at?
我也是
Me too.
很好  那就有个喜欢我名字的人跟我同桌了
Good. Now there'll be someone there who likes my name.
对  没错
Yes, there will.
猜怎么着  莫莉·吉柏特
Guess what, Molly Gilbert.
你刚刚被踢到一号桌了
You've just been bumped up to table one.
如果你没有意见的话
And if it's all right with you,
我要代替你坐到六号桌
I'll take your place at table six.
马丁·利格拉齐
Martin Llegglachen.
这样好多了  现在双手弯曲
That's better. Now, just bend your arms a little bit.
眼睛看前方
Now look straight ahead.
这次我要你臀部用力顶
Okay, this time I want you to really put your ass into it.
钱德勒  你看我的男伴终于来了
Chandler, darling, look, my date has finally arrived.
这位是丹尼斯·菲利浦斯
I'd like you to meet Dennis Phillips.
恭喜  谢谢
Congratulations. Thank you.
丹尼斯是我的老朋友...
Yes, Dennis is a dear old friend...
还是个绝佳情人
...and a fantastic lover.
太棒了  丹尼斯  谢谢你取悦我老妈
Bravo, Dennis. Thanks for pleasing my mother so.
抱歉我没赶上婚礼  我在忙着试镜
I'm so sorry I missed the ceremony. I was stuck at auditions.
对  丹尼斯正在执导一出百老汇新戏
Yes, Dennis is directing a new Broadway show.
我们应该还没见过  乔伊·崔比安尼
I don't believe we've met. Joey Tribbiani.
丹尼斯·菲利浦斯
Dennis Phillips.
多年来我一直很欣赏你的作品
I've admired your work for years.
你的作品真的很棒  谢谢
You've done some really amazing stuff. Thank you.
失陪一下  我要去喝点东西
If you'll excuse me, I'm gonna go get myself a drink.
我马上回来
I'll be back in a moment.
丹尼斯·菲利浦斯  真是太棒了
Dennis Phillips. That's great.
你们怎么认识的
How did you guys meet?
那个故事说起来有趣
Well, it's a funny story.
是惹人发笑  还是惨不忍睹
Funny, "haha"? Or funny:
谢谢  非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
大家请坐
If everyone will please take your seats,
晚宴马上开始
dinner will be served.
我以为你在六号桌  不  是九号桌
I thought you were at table six. No. Nine.
你刚刚给我看时是那样拿的...
See, before, when you showed it to me, you held it that way...
我被你误导了
...which was misleading.
你们好
Hello.
你能请你妈把我的履历表
Will you see if your mom
拿给丹尼斯·菲利浦斯吗
can give my resume to Dennis Phillips?
只要能演百老汇舞台剧  我就什么戏都演过了
If I could get in a Broadway show, then I would've done it all.
电影  电视剧跟舞台剧
Film, television and theater.
唯一的例外是广播剧
The only thing left would be radio.
那是留给丑八怪演的
But that's just for ugly people.
你穿几号鞋  11号  11号半
What size shoes do you wear? 11, 11 half.
我的鞋子太滑没办法跳舞
Great. My shoes give me a problem on the dance floor.
你的戏靴能借我吗
Can I borrow your boots from your costume?
我真不知道把靴子丢到哪里去了  抱歉
I don't really even know where I left those. Sorry.
你的脚不可能是11号半
Those aren't 11 half.
好吧  我穿七号的鞋子
Okay, fine, I'm a 7!
我的脚出奇的小
I have surprisingly small feet.
但其它部份都很大  我可以露给你看
But the rest of me is good. I'll show you.
你能相信菲比怀孕了吗
Can you believe Phoebe got pregnant?
现在别谈那件事了
You know what, honey? Let's not talk about that right now.
这可是爆炸性新闻
This is so huge.
没错  但那也没有你的婚礼重要
Sure, but as big as your wedding?
当然  我的婚礼最重要了
Of course not. Nothing is.
说句悄悄话  到了这个时代...
Between me and you, in this day and age...
谁会笨到让自己怀孕
...how dumb do you have to be to get pregnant?
有时候你该做的都做了
You know? Sometimes you can do everything right.
双方都戴上了该戴的东西
Everyone wears what they're supposed to wear...
但有个小家伙还是攻过了城池
...and one of those little guys just gets through.
怎么会呢
How?
我不知道  或许它们有什么工具
I don't know. Maybe they have tools.
我跟她谈过  她要把孩子生下来
Well, I talked to her, and she's definitely gonna have the baby.
她说她要自己抚养孩子
She said she's gonna raise it on her own.
或许那真的很勇敢
Well, maybe that's really brave.
或许吧  我只是希望她知道那有多辛苦
Maybe. I just hope she realizes how hard it's gonna be.
或许她没有想那么多
Maybe she hasn't really thought it through that much.
的确有很多事需要考虑
Well, there's a lot to think about.
她要怎么解决经济问题
How is she gonna handle this financially?
她怎么能应付得了工作
How is she gonna juggle work?
她知道她在未来的18年内
Does she realize she's not gonna have a date again
都没法再去约会了吗
for the next, like, 18 years?
我不知道
I don't know.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我只是想到菲比怀了孕  可怜的菲比
I'm just thinking about Phoebe. Poor, knockedup Phoebe.
要喝香槟吗
Champagne?
好的  谢谢你
Oh, yes! Thank you very much.
法国人都是那样喝香槟的
That's actually how the French drink it.
我刚刚跟我的情人詹姆斯·布洛林通过电话
Well, I just got off the phone with my lover James Brolin.
真的吗
Oh, really?
他显然娶了一个歌手
Yes. Apparently, he is married to some singer.
但他说他会为了我离开她
But he said he'd leave her for me.
我说"詹姆斯·布洛林  你确定吗"
And I said, "James, James Brolin, are you sure?"
詹姆斯·布洛林说...
James Brolin said...
怀孕的人是瑞秋
Rachel's really the one who's pregnant?
什么
What?!
装得那么费劲干嘛
Why bother?
你感觉如何  我不知道我有什么感觉
How do you feel? I don't know. I don't know how I feel.
一切都发生得太快了
This is all happening so fast.
我得做出许多我不想做的决定
I have to make all these decisions that I don't wanna make.
谁快把这玩意拿走
Someone just take this away from me!
冷静点  或许你没有怀孕  什么
Calm down. Maybe you're not pregnant. What?!
我怀三胞胎的时候
When I got pregnant with the triplets,
也验了三次孕才确定
I took that test, like, three times just to make sure.
对  或许是假警报
Yes. Maybe it's a false positive.
你确定你在验孕棒上尿的方式没错吗
Are you sure you peed on the stick right?
不然我要怎么尿才对
How many ways are there to do that?
我是说在没有百分之百确定前别大惊小怪
I'm just saying, don't freak out until you're 100 percent sure.
好吧  我回家后会再验一次
All right, I'll take it again when I get home.
你可以现在验
You gotta take it now.
就当成送我的礼物吧
Do it as a present to me.
好吧  谢谢你  好的
Okay, thank you. Okay.
我去帮你买验孕棒
I'll run out and get you one.
你们真是太好了
You girls are so great.
等一下  孩子他爸是谁
Wait a minute. Who's the father?
她不肯告诉我们
She won't tell us.
快说吧  这可是我的婚礼
Come on! It's my wedding.
你可以把这当做是送我的礼物
That could be my present!
我刚刚答应为了你验孕
I just gave you peeing on a stick.
看吧  所以一定要做礼物登记
See, this is why you register.
又是椅子的声音  好吗  我没放
It was the chair again. Okay? I'm not doing it!
这样吧
It was... Look, you know what?
你想跳舞吗  好啊
Would you like to dance? Sure.
太棒了
Great.
盖勒博士  我没有放屁
Dr. Geller. I wasn't farting!
那是我们那一桌玩的小游戏
A little game from our table.
什么事  盖勒博士  你愿意跟我跳舞吗
Yes? Dr. Geller, will you dance with me?
或许待会再说  现在我要跟这位小姐跳舞
Maybe later. Right now, I'm about to dance with this lady.
好吧
Okay.
除非这位小姐不介意让你插队
Unless this lady wouldn't mind letting you go first.
我很乐意  你太好心了
I'd be happy to. You are very sweet.
没错  我确实好心
Yes, I am.
我们来试试我的绝招
In fact, why don't we try my special way?
你可以踩在我的脚上跳舞
You can dance on my feet.
没问题  是吗  跳上来吧
Sure. Yeah? Hop on.
那个美丽的小姐在看吗  在
Is the pretty lady looking? Uhhuh.
继续跳
Keep dancing.
世上无人将欣赏到这般舞姿
And the world will never know.
你跟丹尼斯提过我的事了吗
Did you talk to Dennis about me yet?
我跟他提到你非常有天份
Yes. I told him how talented you were
还有《我们的日子》的事
and I told him all about Days of our Lives.
不不不  你不能把那种事告诉百老汇导演
No, no, no! You don't tell a Broadway guy that!
现在他会以为我只是个肥皂剧演员
Now he thinks I'm just a soap actor.
但你不只是肥皂剧演员
But you're not just a soap actor.
你是长了双小脚的肥皂剧演员
You are a soap actor with freakishly tiny feet.
谢谢  不  谢谢你  米兰达
Thank you. No, thank you, Miranda.
是梅玲达  好吧
Melinda. All right.
那简直太可爱了
How cute was that?
你在看我们吗
Oh, were you watching?
下一个能跟我跳吗
Can I go next?
当然可以  来吧
Of course you can. Hop on.
好吧  但我要排在她后面
Okay, but I get to hop on after her.
我一定能"得分" 什么
I am so gonna score. What?
我喜欢你的蝴蝶结
I like your bow.
我要请大家举杯向莫妮卡及钱德勒致意
I'd like to propose a toast to Monica and Chandler...
他们是全世界最般配的夫妻
...the greatest couple in the world,
也是我最好的朋友
and my best friends.
我刚听说他们要结婚时
When I first found out they were getting married,
我有点生气
I was... I was a little angry.
我心想"天啊  为什么
I was like, "Why, God? Why?
你为什么要把他们从我身边抢走"
How can you take them away from me!"
然后我回想起我们之间有过的回忆
But then I thought back over all our memories together.
快乐的回亿
Some happy memories.
还有悲伤的回亿
And there were some sad memories.
对不起
I'm sorry.
还有可怕的回亿
And some scared memories.
然后我才发现  我永远都会是他们的朋友
And then I realized I'll always be their friend.
他们这个朋友会说好几种方言
Their friend who can speak in many dialects...
接受过舞台训练
...and has training in stage combat
愿意拍部份裸露的戏份
and is willing to do partial nudity.
敬这对金童玉女
To the happy couple.
谢谢  刚才跳得很棒  艾许莉
Thank you. That was very nice, Ashley.
我们能再跳一次吗   不行
Can we do it again? No, no.
现在轮到我了吗  我是下一个
So, is it my turn now? I'm next.
没关系  你可以先跟她跳
That's okay, you can dance with her first.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
好吧
Okay.
你叫什么名字  葛特
Okay, so, what's your name? Gert.
名字真美
That's pretty.
你想要做什么  葛特
What are you doing there, Gert?
跟其他女孩一样踩在你脚上跳舞
Dancing on your feet like the other girls did it.
好吧
Okay.
跳上来吧  葛特
Hop on, Gert.
你的脚为什么不动
Why aren't you moving your feet?
我在努力了
I'm trying.
快一点  你跳得太慢了
Faster. You're not going fast enough.
或许我该踩在你脚上
Maybe I should stand on your feet!
你听到我的致词了吗
So did you happen to catch my toast up there?
天啊  你那么做是为了我
Oh, my God. That was for my benefit?
我那么做是为了所有人
There was a little something for everyone.
我知道你在为新戏选角
I know you're casting for this new show.
我觉得你不适合这部戏
Look, Joey. I don't think you're right for this project.
你这就错了吧
See, that's where you're wrong.
不论是什么戏  我都能演
Whatever it is, I can do it.
如果你对刚刚的表演不满意  考考我
If you didn't see it up there, just try me.
那出戏的演员全是中国人
It's an all Chinese cast.
你可以变成中国人吗
Can you be Chinese?
我不以此为荣  但是...
Well, I'm not proud of this, but...
天啊  求求你别那么做
Oh, my God. No, no, no. Please don't!
准备重回舞池了吗
Ready to get back to the dance floor?
它变成沙地了吗
Did it turn into sand?
我喜欢这首歌  你会跳得很好的
Come on, I love this song. Come on. You'll be fine.
不  我跳不好
No. No, I won't.
你知道为什么我要去上舞蹈课吗
Do you know why I took all those lessons?
我不希望让别人看到
For the first time, I didn't want you to be embarrassed
你跟一个跳梁小丑跳舞  丢光了脸
to be seen on the dance floor with some clumsy idiot.
老公  你绝不会让我出丑
Oh, sweetie, you could never embarrass me.
好吧  你很容易就会让我出丑
Okay, you could easily embarrass me.
但那不重要  好吗
But it doesn't matter, all right?
我嫁给你了
I married you.
我要在新婚之夜跟我丈夫跳舞  来吧
So I'm gonna dance on my wedding night with my husband. Come on.
尽量不要移动你的脚
Just try not to move your feet at all.
这就对了
There you go.
钱德勒  我要叫警察逮捕你  为什么
Chandler, I'm gonna have you arrested. Why?
你偷了我的舞步
You stole my moves!
还要多久  30秒
How much longer? 30 seconds.
30秒  好吧
Thirty seconds, okay...
我错过了吗
Did I miss it?
瑞秋
Rachel.
你要知道  如果是阳性反应  我们会...
I want you to know that if it's positive, we're gonna...
我知道  你知道  好吧
I know. I know. You do. Okay.
时候到了
It's time.
别进来
No!
来吧  瑞秋
Go ahead, Rach.
等一下  我不敢看
Wait. You know what? I can't look at it. I can't look at it.
谁帮我看一下告诉我
Somebody else tell me. Somebody else tell me.
好吧
Okay.
是阴性反应
It's negative.
什么  是阴性反应
What? It's negative.
真相大白了
Well, there you go.
太棒了  这真是个天大的好消息
That is... That's great. That is really great, great news.
因为这整件事...
You know, because the whole...
我在经济方面还没有准备好  所以...
...not being ready and, kind of, the financial aspects, all that...
事情本来就应该是这样的
This is so just the way that this was supposed to be.
那就太棒了
Then, great.
天啊  我真是太蠢了
God, this is so stupid.
我怎么会为了我从未拥有过的东西难过
How can I be upset over something I never had?
是阴性反应吗
It's negative?
不  是阳性反应
No, it's positive.
什么  不是阴性反应  是阳性反应
What? It's not negative, it's positive.
你确定吗  对  我刚刚说了谎
Are you sure? Yeah, I lied before.
天啊
My god.
现在你知道自己的真实感受了
Now you know how you really feel about it.
那可真是个危险的小把戏
That's a risky little game.
你真的要把孩子生下来吗
Are you really gonna do this?
对
Yeah.
我要把孩子生下来
I'm gonna have a baby.
我要有孩子了
I'm gonna have a baby!
孩子他爸是谁  不  现在还不是时候
With who? No, it's still not the time.
我不知道接下来是首快歌
I just didn't see the fast song coming.
别说话  我们送你回房间让你泡泡脚
Don't try to talk, we'll get you up to your room, soak your feet.
你会没事的
You'll be okay.
谢谢  那真的是太好心了
Thank you. That is so sweet!
不  我是认真的  现在好男人不多了
No, I mean it. There are so few genuinely nice guys out there.
可不是嘛
Tell me about it.
我简直感觉自己是在孤军奋斗
I feel like I'm holding down the fort by myself.
你是乔伊  对吧  对
It's Joey, right? Yeah.
等一下  不要
Wait a minute! No!
我才是好人
I'm the nice one!
整晚跟孩子们跳舞的人是我
I'm the one that danced with the kids all night. I...
你的脚好小啊
How small are your feet?!